# **CURRICULUM VITAE**



Dr Fadzilah binti Ishak

Medical Officer UD54

Pejabat Kesihatan Daerah Port Dickson

Negeri Sembilan

0126254299, dr.fadzilah@moh.gov.my

Alternative email: <a href="mailto:ilah3369@yahoo.com.my">ilahishak78@gmail.com</a>

#### **PROFILE**

I am a senior Medical Officer graduated from University Sains Malaysia (USM) in year 2002 and have been in the service for 17 years. Recently, received a Master Degree on Healthcare Management (Master in Business Administration). Personally I am good in working in team, goal oriented person, friendly and punctual.

## **EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE**

1. House Officer, Hospital Melaka : July 2002 – Jun 2003

- Medical Posting
- Surgical Posting
- O&G Posting

2. Medical Officer, Hospital Melaka : July 2003 – July 20024

- Orthopaedic Posting
- Paediatric Posting

Emergency and Trauma Department

### 3. Medical Officer, Klinik Kesihatan Port Dickson, PKD PD, N.Sembilan

• Outpatient clinic : Aug 2004 - 2006

Maternal and Child Health Clinic : 2006 - 2011
NCD Clinic/Outpatient Clinic : 2012 - 2015
As Medical Officer In Charge of the clinic : 2015 - 2018
Internal Auditor of ISO 9001 : 2009 - Now
Lead Auditor : 2011 - 2015
Management Representative : 2016 - Now

## 4. Medical Officer, Pejabat Kesihatan Port Dickson

In Charge of NCD and KOSPEN program at district level : 2019

Management Representative of ISO 9001:2015 : 2016 - Now

#### **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS**

Degree of Medicine 2002
 Universiti Sains Malaysia
 Kampus Kubang Kerian, Kelantan

Master Degree in Business Administration (Healthcare Management) 2019
 Universiti Teknologi Malaysia
 Skudai, Johor

#### **AWARDS**

Anugerah Perkhidmatan Cemerlang, Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri Sembilan; 2008 Anugerah Perkhidmatan Cemerlang, Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri Sembilan; 2012

## PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIPS

Member of Alumni MBA Healthcare

#### TRAINING AND ATTACHMENT

1) Internal Audit Course MS ISO 9001:2015

## 28-29 Ogos 2017

- 2) Kursus Pengukuhan Pemantapan MEETS Tahun 2017 22-23 Mac 2017
- Kursus Pengukuhan Peranan Pegawai Perubatan Y/M Klinik
   April 2017
- 4) National Tuberculosis & Lung Diseases Conference 20161-3 April 2016
- 5) Bengkel Pelaksanaan Projek PSK 1-3 Jun 2016
- 6) Taklimat Garispanduan Pelaksanaan Klinik Rakan Bayi 2015 28-30 Oktober 2015
- 7) O&G Update 2014 9-10 Julai 2014
- 8) Bengkel Kajian Kes Perinatal Peringkat Negeri Sembilan 2008 11-13 Ogos 2008
- Kursus Kenegaraan SSM PTK1
   1-5 Mac 2007

#### PROGRAMMES COORDINATOR

- Pegawai Perubatan Penyelaras Program Kawalan TB di Pringkat Daerah (2016- 2018)
- 2) Quality Management System MS ISO 9001 (2009 2019)
- 3) Health Promoting Clinic Programme 2017

### **FACILITATOR**

- 1) Panel Penilai Pengiktirafan Klinik rakan Bayi, Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri Sembilan, 2016 2019
- 2) Trainer of Breastfeeding Course, 2011 2018
- 3) Konvensyen Panel Penasihat Klinik Kesihatan Peringkat Daerah PD, 2017

### **REFEREES**

- Dr Noor Khalili bin Mohd Ali
   Pakar Perubatan Kesihatan Awam
   Pegawai Kesihatan Daerah Port Dickson
   KM 2, Jalan Seremban
   Port Dickson
   Negeri Sembilan
   0195789454
   drkhaliliali@moh.gov.my
- 2) Dato' Dr Zainuddin bin Mohd Ali Pakar Perubatan Kesihatan Awam Pengarah Kesihatan Negeri Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri Sembilan 0132189811 drzainuddin@gmail.com